

PROFILE

baotrung.ylk@gmail.com

0964953205

District 8, Ho Chi Minh City

SKILLS

USING FAST SOFTWARE PROFESSIONALLY

USING EXCEL PROFESSIONALLY

ACCOUNTING TRANSACTION POSTING

TEAMWORK SKILL

CERTIFICATIONS

2022

TOEIC certificate 2 skills - Reading: 335, Listening: 305

2020

IT certificate IC3 GS4

INTERESTS

Reading book, listening to music, ...

PHAN TRAN BAO TRUNG **GENERAL ACCOUNTANT**

OBJECTIVE

I have 4 months of auditing internship experience, nearly 1 year of full-time work experience in application consulting, 1 year 9 months of full-time work experience in accounting and tax consulting. I am proficient in using accounting, ERP software of FAST, preparing FS and tax reports. I am looking forward to working as an General Accountant at your company to contribute to fulfilling the company's job requirements.

WORK EXPERIENCE



ACCOUNTING AND TAX CONSULTANT // 04/2023 - 12/2024

I-GLOCAL COMPANY LIMITED - HO CHI MINH CITY BRANCH

- Perform work as directed by superiors.
- Enter data and prepare Financial Statements and accounting books for clients.
- Prepare monthly, quarterly and annual tax records/reports (including PIT, CIT, VAT and FCT).
- Review Financial Statements and periodic tax reports for clients.
- Support accounting and tax consulting work for superiors.



BRANCH OF BUSINESS MANAGEMENT SOFTWARE JOINT STOCK COMPANY IN HO **CHI MINH CITY**

- Survey and analyze customer requirements.
- Collaborate with the Programming Department to design software according to customer requirements.
- Install, guide, and support customers in using the software.
- Assist customers with accounting, human resources, and customer relations tasks.

AUDIT ASSISTANT INTERN // 12/2021 - 03/2022

AS AUDITING COMPANY

- Perform auditing tasks assigned by the audit team leader.
- Collaborate with the team leader to conduct the auditing process from planning, execution, to summarization and report writing.
- Provide consulting support to clients on issues related to accounting policies, finance, taxes, and relevant legal documents.
- · Assist the team leader in designing, organizing, and checking the accounting system, internal controls, evaluating, and processing financial information.

EDUCATION



CORPORATE ACCOUNTING // 2018 - 2022

University of Economics Ho Chi Minh City

Graduation classified distinct - GPA: 8.12